GURTEJ SINGH

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



/gurtej-singh-336621224/



gurtej154@gmail.com



https://github.com/gurtej154

I am a Freelancer, extensively experienced in Graphic Designing, UI/UX Designing, Full-Stack Development and Architectural Drafting. With the current skillsets and experiences in my possession, I would like to collaborate within the Tech industry and further develop my knowledge.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ARCHITECTURAL INTERN

2019 - 2019 | John Holland 3 months

MINER

2019 - 2021 | BHP 18 months

FREELANCER

2020 - Present | Self-employed

WEB PROJECTS

INSTANT CRYPTO

A front-End application with third-party API integration, to allow users to view crypto currency valuations of a coin and news articles around it.

REPOSITORY:

https://github.com/gurtej154/InstantCrypto

DEPLOYED:

https://gurtej154.github.io/InstantCrypto/

COINANCE

A MERN Stack web application with third-party API integration, allows the user to create a account and add coins of their choice to their dashboard.

REPOSITORY:

https://github.com/gurtej154/Coinance

DEPLOYED:

https://coinance-crypto-tracker.herokuapp.com/

EDUCATION

2016-2018

CURTIN UNIVERSITY
Bachelor of Applied Science
(Architectural Science)

2011-2015

RENMARK HIGH SCHOOL

Completed Secondary Schooling and attained SACE certification

SKILLS

- Web Design
- Design Thinking
- Wireframe Creation
- Front-End Development
- Back-End Development
- Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- Graphic Designing
- UI/UX Designing

CERTIFICATION

2021-2022

THE UNIVERSITY OF ADELAIDE
Coding Bootcamp - Web Development

2021- Present

CODECADEMY

Full-Stack Engineer (career pathway)